Jane Harman Papers, 1960-1998 (ongoing) (bulk 1993-1998)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. CONSTITUENT SERVICES 1993-98
  - District concerns
    - Welfare, 1994-98
      - CLARE Foundation (Box 203, Folder 22)
      - South Bay counseling grant (Box 203, Folder 23)
      - Welfare reform (Box 203, Folder 24)
      - Wisconsin welfare waiver (Box 203, Folder 25)
    - Women, 1995-98
      - 1736 Family Crisis Center (Box 203, Folder 26)
      - Contact lists (Box 203, Folder 27)
      - Harbor Interfaith Shelter HUD grant (Box 203, Folder 28)
      - NARAL (Box 203, Folder 29)
      - Partial birth abortion ban (Box 203, Folder 30)
      - Planned Parenthood meeting, 8 Oct 1996 (Box 203, Folder 31)
      - U.N. Women's Conference (Box 203, Folder 32)
      - U.N. Women's Conference one year later (Box 203, Folder 33)
      - Weddington (Box 203, Folder 34)
      - Women and Children First (Box 203, Folder 35)
      - Women's event, 26 Aug 1995 (Box 203, Folder 36)
      - Women's Roundtable (Box 203, Folder 37)
    - North end of district issues
      - Lawndale: correspondence, Planned Parenthood, projects (Box 203, Folder 38-40)
      - Marina del Rey, 1997-98 (Box 203)
        - Ballona Lagoon Marine Preserve (Box 203, Folder 41)
        - Ballona Wetlands, [see also Oversize Materials-Flat file] (Box 204, Folder 1)
        - Ballona Wetlands Land Trust (Box 204, Folder 2)
        - Chabad of the Marina (Box 204, Folder 3)
        - Dredging, 1998 - south entrance (Box 204, Folder 4)
        - Emergency dredging (Box 204, Folder 5)
        - Friends of Ballona Wetlands (Box 204, Folder 6)
        - Marina del Rey dredging (Box 204, Folder 7-9)
        - Marina del Rey dredging - boat tour (Box 204, Folder 10)
        - Marina issues (Box 204, Folder 11)
        - Playa Vista/DreamWorks (Box 204, Folder 12)
        - Weiss, Malcolm (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Venice, 1994-98
        - Beethoven Elementary School - Netday 1996 (Box 205, Folder 2)
        - Habitat for Humanity (Box 205, Folder 3)
        - Holiday Venice Apartments (Box 205, Folder 4)
        - Los Angeles Unified School District (Box 205, Folder 5)
        - Oceanview Apartments (Box 205, Folder 6)
        - Open house, Apr 1997 (Box 205, Folder 7)
        - Phoenix House (Box 205, Folder 8)
        - Satellite office (Box 205, Folder 9)
        - St. Joseph Center (Box 205, Folder 10)
        - Venice Arts Mecca (Box 205, Folder 11)
        - Venice Boardwalk Association/Venice Action Committee (Box 205, Folder 12)
        - Venice Community Housing Corporation (Box 205, Folder 13)
        - Venice Family Clinic (Box 205, Folder 14)
        - Venice High School - Science Bowl (Box 205, Folder 15)
        - Venice Roundtable (Box 205, Folder 16)
        - Venice/Marina Chamber Roundtable (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - Westchester, 1994-97
        - Chamber of Commerce Installation Dinner (Box 205, Folder 18)
        - Chamber of Commerce newsletters (Box 205, Folder 19)
        - Flight Path (Box 205, Folder 20)
    - South end of district issues
      - Avalon, 1995-98 (Box 205)
        - Catalina Island: 1996, bills, trips (Box 205, Folder 21-24)
        - Cruise ships legislation (Box 205, Folder 25)
        - FEMA (Box 205, Folder 26)
        - Gangway inspections (Box 206, Folder 1)
        - General (Box 206, Folder 2)
        - Loyola Marymount University (Box 206, Folder 3)
        - Otis College (Box 206, Folder 4)
        - Santa Monica College (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - El Segundo, 1994-97
        - Chamber of Commerce - Government Affairs Committee (Box 206, Folder 6)
        - City (Box 206, Folder 7)
        - Issues (Box 206, Folder 8)
        - Mail trouble (Box 206, Folder 9)
        - Schools (Box 206, Folder 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 206, Folder 11)
      - Gardena Valley Democratic Club, 1996 (Box 206, Folder 12)
      - Hermosa Beach, 1993-98
        - City (Box 206, Folder 13)
        - Schools (Box 206, Folder 14)
        - Veterans - Tolliver, Ghidoni (Box 206, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 206, Folder 16)
      - Lomita, 1996-98
        - Harbor Hills Housing Development/HUD (Box 206, Folder 17)
        - Issues (Box 206, Folder 18)
        - Lomita Little League (Box 206, Folder 19)
        - Post office substation (Box 206, Folder 20)
        - POW flag (Box 206, Folder 21)
      - Manhattan Beach, 1994-98
        - City (Box 206, Folder 22)
        - Manhattan Beach Coordinating Council (Box 206, Folder 23)
        - Mira Costa High School (Box 206, Folder 24)
        - Pacific Elementary School (Box 207, Folder 1)
        - Schools (Box 207, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - Palos Verdes, 1995-98
        - Chadwick School - Lyon, Mueggler (Box 207, Folder 4)
        - Issues (Box 207, Folder 5)
        - Landslides/Palos Verdes Peninsula Land Conservancy (Box 207, Folder 6)
        - Natural Communities Conservation Planning (NCCP) (Box 207, Folder 7)
        - Palos Verdes Democratic Club (Box 207, Folder 8)
        - Palos Verdes Peninsula Unified School District (Box 207, Folder 9-10)
        - Peninsula Education Foundation (Box 207, Folder 11)
        - Peninsula Seniors (Box 207, Folder 12)
        - Rancho Palos Verdes - Mayor Byrd meeting (Box 207, Folder 13)
        - Rohrabacher, Dana - Chamber of Commerce (Box 207, Folder 14)
        - Ruth, Col. Francis David (Box 207, Folder 15)
      - Redondo Beach, 1994-98
        - Chamber of Commerce (Box 207, Folder 16-17)
        - City (Box 207, Folder 18)
        - Edison plant (Box 207, Folder 19)
        - Issues, miscellaneous (Box 207, Folder 20)
        - Schools (Box 207, Folder 21)
      - Torrance, 1995-98
        - Chamber of Commerce (Box 207)
          - Part 1 (Box 207, Folder 22-23)
          - Part 2 (Box 208, Folder 1-2)
        - City (Box 208, Folder 3)
        - Federal Communications Commission (Box 208, Folder 4)
        - Housing (Box 208, Folder 5)
        - Issues (Box 208, Folder 6)
        - Knolls Lodge/Knolls Manor Mobile Home Parks (Box 208, Folder 7)
        - North High School ROTC (Box 208, Folder 8)
        - Olympic Torch Relay (Box 208, Folder 9)
        - Organizations (Box 208, Folder 10)
        - Radio frequencies (Box 208, Folder 11)
        - Schools (Box 208, Folder 12)
        - Torrance Coordinating Council (Box 208, Folder 13)
        - Zip code change (Box 208, Folder 14)
  - District visits
    - Jan-Jul 1994, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS-Constituent services-Events/district activities] (Box 208, Folder 15-17)
    - Sep 1994 - Jul 1995 (Box 209, Folder 1-16)
    - Aug-Dec 1995 (Box 210, Folder 1-15)
    - Jan-13 Jun 1996 (Box 211, Folder 1-4)
    - 21 Jun - Dec 1996 (Box 212, Folder 1-7)
    - Jan-Jul 1997 (Box 213, Folder 1-8)
    - Aug-Nov 1997 (Box 214, Folder 1-7)
    - Dec 1997 - Nov 1998 (Box 215, Folder 1-10)
  - Constituent requests, 1994-97
    - Constituent responses, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS-Political activities-House races] (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Referrals/forwarded letters (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Requests (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Requests completed (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Response form letters
    - Draft responses, 1995-97 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Final responses (Box 216, Folder 6-9)
    - Form letters, 1993-98, undated (Box 217, Folder 1-8)
    - Letter library, 1996 (Box 217, Folder 9-10)
    - Responses, 1995-98 (Box 218, Folder 1-2)
  - Response correspondence
    - Call sheets, Mar 1993 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Constituent responses, 103rd-104th Congress (Box 218, Folder 4-7)
    - Harman office responses (Box 218)
      - Feb-Jul 1993 (Box 218, Folder 8-13)
      - Aug 1993 - Feb 1994 (Box 219, Folder 1-5)
    - Mail reports, Jun-Aug 1993 (Box 219, Folder 6)
- SERIES VI. MEDIA ACTIVITIES 1994-98
  - Publications and mailings, 1995-98 (Box 219)
    - Farewell remarks (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Issue position papers (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - "Legislative Happenings" (Box 219)
      - 104th-105th Congress, 1st session (Box 219, Folder 9-11)
      - 105th Congress, 2nd session (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Promotional materials (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Web page update (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - General
    - Press file, 1998 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Press releases/op-ed pieces, 1994-98, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 220, Folder 5-8)
    - Public speeches/drafts/talking points, 1995-98 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - Aug 1994 - Aug 1996 (Box 221, Folder 2-11)
    - Sep 1996 - Mar 1998 (Box 222, Folder 1-9)
    - Mar-May 1998 (Box 223, Folder 1-10)
    - May-Nov 1998 (Box 224, Folder 1-10)
- SERIES VII. OFFICE ADMINISTRATION 1993-98
  - Chief of Staff files (Box 224)
    - Bill Black, 1993 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Mark Kadesh, 1995-97 (Box 225, Folder 2-12)
    - Mike Monasmith, 1997-98 (Box 225)
      - Correspondence and notes (Box 225)
        - Part 1 (Box 225, Folder 13-14)
        - Part 2 (Box 226, Folder 1-3)
      - District visit, Nov 1997 (Box 226, Folder 4)
      - Gay/lesbian suicides (Box 226, Folder 5)
      - Hughes/China, Nov 1997 (Box 226, Folder 6)
      - Israel trip (Box 226, Folder 7)
      - LAX Town Hall, Dec 1997 (Box 226, Folder 8)
      - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) (Box 226, Folder 9)
      - Proposition K - "K for Kids" (Box 226, Folder 10)
      - Republicans for Harman (Box 226, Folder 11)
      - Staffing (Box 226, Folder 12)
      - Torrance Chamber visit to DC (Box 226, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 226, Folder 14)
  - Office files
    - The "Bible"-103rd (Box 226, Folder 15)
    - Guestbook, 1993-95 (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Scheduling memos (Box 227)
      - 25 May 1994-22 May 1997 (Box 227, Folder 2-7)
      - 29 May 1997-28 Oct 1998 (Box 228, Folder 1-3)
    - Staffing (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - General (Box 228)
      - 103rd: House rules, staff, trip file (Box 228, Folder 5-7)
      - 104th
        - Strategic plans, 1995-96 (Box 228, Folder 8-11)
        - C-MANC schedule (Box 229, Folder 1)
        - Harman's favorite prayer by House Chaplain (Box 229, Folder 2)
      - 105th
        - Strategic plans, 1997-98 (Box 229, Folder 3-5)
        - AIPAC (Box 229, Folder 6-8)
        - Army Secretary Togo West (Box 229, Folder 9)
        - Arts caucus activities (Box 229, Folder 10)
        - Bosnia trip, Dec 1995 (Box 229, Folder 11)
        - Bradley, Tom - funeral services (Box 229, Folder 12)
        - California Delegation - memo to Gray Davis (Box 229, Folder 13)
        - California Delegation Task Force (Box 229, Folder 14)
        - California Institute (Box 229, Folder 15-16)
        - California Realtors (Box 229, Folder 17)
        - California Women Lawyers (Box 230, Folder 1)
        - Call Your Congresswoman proposal (Box 230, Folder 2)
        - Chambers of commerce (Box 230, Folder 3)
        - City of Los Angeles bond committee (Box 230, Folder 4)
        - CODEL Goss, Dec 1997 (Box 230, Folder 5)
        - Congressional Women's Caucus, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 230, Folder 6)
        - Cosponsor forms (Box 230, Folder 7)
        - DCCC vote analysis of Harman (Box 230, Folder 8)
        - District schools (Box 230, Folder 9)
        - Economic diversification project (Box 230)
          - Part 1 (Box 230, Folder 10-12)
          - Part 2 (Box 231, Folder 1-3)
        - Economic plan, 1993-5th anniversary (Box 231, Folder 4)
        - Ethics rules (Box 231, Folder 5-6)
        - Flag etiquette (Box 231, Folder 7)
        - Freshmen August 1997 recess highlights (Box 231, Folder 8)
        - Fundraising comparison (Box 231, Folder 9)
        - Gingrich, ethics investigation (Box 232, Folder 1-2)
        - Guest registration card (Box 232, Folder 3)
        - Harman legislative/district accomplishments (Box 232, Folder 4)
        - Harvard Law (Box 232, Folder 5)
        - Harvard seminar, 13 Nov 1998 (Box 232, Folder 6)
        - Hate mail (Box 232, Folder 7)
        - House rules, 105th Congress (Box 232, Folder 8)
        - Kenny Nickelson Memorial Foundation (Box 232, Folder 9)
        - Labor standards overseas (Box 232, Folder 10)
        - Marine Exchange of LA-Long Beach (Box 232, Folder 11)
        - Maritime Advisory Committee/maritime issues memos (Box 232, Folder 12)
        - Muka v. The Rutherford Institute, et al. (Box 232, Folder 13)
        - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) (Box 232, Folder 14)
        - National Restaurant Association (Box 233, Folder 1)
        - National Taxpayers Union (NTU) (Box 233, Folder 2)
        - New Democrats on education (Box 233, Folder 3)
        - North Korea Intel trip, Aug 1997 (Box 233, Folder 4)
        - Official expenses - Harman return to Treasury (Box 233, Folder 5)
        - Payroll (Box 233, Folder 6)
        - Ratings (Box 233)
          - Part 1 (Box 233, Folder 7-10)
          - Part 2 (Box 234, Folder 1-2)
        - Reception for Harman: Washington, D.C., district (Box 234, Folder 3-4)
        - Sanchez, Loretta (Box 234, Folder 5)
        - Secretary of the Army (Box 234, Folder 6)
        - Sexual misconduct in the military, Sep 1997 (Box 234, Folder 7)
        - Staff lists (Box 234, Folder 8)
        - State of the Union address, 1998 (Box 234, Folder 9)
        - Strange things (Box 234, Folder 10)
        - Team California (Box 234, Folder 11)
        - United Nations Conference on Women (Box 234, Folder 12)
        - United States Chamber of Commerce (Box 234, Folder 13)
        - Veterans Day, 1997 (Box 234, Folder 14)
        - Votes where Democrats made a difference (Box 234, Folder 15)
        - Women's Vote Project, 1998 (Box 234, Folder 16)
  - District Office Updates, 1994-1998
    - 14 Apr 1994-13 Oct 1995 (Box 235, Folder 1-5)
    - 20 Oct 1995-21 Mar 1997 (Box 236, Folder 1-6)
    - 4 Apr 1997-16 Oct 1998 (Box 237, Folder 1-6)
  - Reference materials
    - 103rd Congress (Box 237)
      - Regulations on the Use of the Congressional Frank (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Highlights of the House Ethics Rules (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - U.S. House Communications Manual (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - New Member-elect Orientation (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - 104th Congress
      - Congressional Liaison Handbook (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Democratic Press Secretary Manual-1996 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - 1996 Directory of Public Information Contacts (Box 238, Folder 7)
      - Members' Congressional Handbook (Box 238, Folder 8)
      - Guide to the Congressional Accountability Act of 1995 (Box 238, Folder 9-10)
    - 105th Congress
      - Democratic Press Secretary Manual-1998 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Revised Members' Congressional Handbook (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - Associated written material for items in SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS (Box 239, Folder 3)
- SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS 1960-98
  - Biographical, 1960, undated (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - Professional activities, 1975-78 (Box 240, Folder 2)
  - Political activities
    - Democratic National Party, 1987-98, undated (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - House campaigns, undated (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - NFIB/Chamber of Commerce, 1995-98 (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Official White House photos, 1994-97 (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Political activities (continued) (Box 240)
    - President Jiang Zemin's visit, 1997 (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Reception for Harman's retirement, 1998 (Box 240, Folder 8-9)
    - Women's Lunch, 1994 (Box 240, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993-97, undated (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - Legislative activities
    - General, 1993-98, [see also Oversize Materials] (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - International politics/issues (Box 241)
      - Bosnia, 1995, undated (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Israel, 1991-97, undated (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Middle East, undated (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - United Nations 4th World Conference on Women - Beijing, 1995 (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - McDonnell Douglas - visit of Dept. of Defense Undersecretary Kaminski, 17 Aug 1995, [see also SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS-Audiotapes-Cassettes] (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Military (Box 241)
      - Fort Jackson (SC) visit, 1998, undated (Box 241, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993-95 (Box 241, Folder 9)
    - Mission to Planet Earth, undated (Box 241, Folder 10)
  - Constituent services
    - Events/district activities, 1995-98, undated (Box 241, Folder 11-12)
    - Photographs with constituents, 1996-98 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - Media activities
    - Harman - alone, 1998, undated (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Publicity photos, undated (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-98 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - Office staff, 1995-96, undated (Box 242, Folder 5)
- SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS 1992-98
  - Audiotapes (Box 242)
    - Cassettes (Box 242)
      - House freshmen interview, Michael Jackson Show, KABC 790, 15 Jan 1993 (Box 243)
      - House freshmen interview, Diane Rehm Show, WAMU, 20 Apr 1993 (Box 243)
      - House freshmen interview, Diane Rehm Show, WAMU, 20 Apr 1993 Michael Jackson Show, 8 Sep 1993; "NAFTA," Which Way L.A., 14 Sep 1993 (Box 243)
      - "Crime Bill Revisited," WWLA, 19 Aug 1994 (Box 243)
      - "Abortion Politics," WWLA, 9 Aug 1995 (Box 243)
      - Harman and Dept. of Defense Undersecretary Kaminski, 17 Aug 1995 (Box 243)
      - "Forum: Defense Spending," KQED FM, 24 Feb 1997 (Box 243)
      - "Gender Integrated Training," Diane Rehm Show, WAMU, 12 May 1997 (Box 243)
      - "LAPD, sex discrimination," Which Way L.A., 12 May 1997; "Segregated training," Which Way L.A., 12 May 1997 (Box 243)
      - "Congresswoman Harman," Michael Jackson Show, 30 Aug 1997 (Box 243)
      - Balanced budget interview with Representative Hefley, undated (Box 243)
      - * Defense bill; Tax cut interview with Representative Hefley, undated (Box 243)
      - "Jackson, Harman and Royce," KABC Talk Radio AM 790, undated (Box 243)
      - Partisanship interview with Representative Hefley, undated (Box 243)
    - Reel-to-reel
      - "Jane Harman," Doak and Shrum, 3 Oct 1994 (Box 244)
  - Computer media, [see Box 265]
    - B-2: A Revolution in Review, Northrop Grumman, CD-ROM (Box 244)
    - Defense Acquisition Deskbook, Department of Defense, version 1.2, 30 Sep 1996 (Box 244)
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress: 1996 election data for 36th district (CA), 3.5" disk (Box 244)
    - The Report of the Department of Defense on Base Realignment and Closure, 2 Apr 1998, version 1.0, CD-ROM (Box 244)
  - Films
    - "Harman," Doak and Shrum, 4 Oct 1994 (Box 245-46)
  - Videotapes
    - Reel-to-reel (Box 245-46)
      - "Jane Harman for Congress," Doak, Shrum, Harris, Carrier and Devine, 13 Oct 1994 (Box 247)
    - 1992
      - "Jane Harman for Congress: Values; Change," Doak, Shrum, Harris, Sherman and Donilon, 26 May 1992 (Box 248)
      - "Jane Harman for Congress: Believe; Narrator; Pro," Doak, Shrum, Harris, Sherman and Donilon, 28 Oct (Box 248)
    - 1993
      - "The California Economy: A Local Government Perspective," Institute for Government Executive Management (IGEM), 4 Feb (Box 248)
      - "The Freshman Class"; "Budget Deal," NBC and CNN, 4 Feb (Box 248)
      - * Nightline, 3 Mar (Box 248)
      - "United We Stand America - Jane Harman Forum," prod. Frank Gaskins, 13 Mar (Box 248)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 16 Apr (Box 248)
      - Washington Week in Review, 22 Apr (Box 248)
      - * Interview regarding Clinton economic package: Deficit reduction, CNN and Company, 21 May (Box 248)
      - * Speech for High Technology Council Awards, 15 Jun (Box 248)
      - "Rep. Cardin with Rep. Harman and Kelly Overman," 17 Jun (Box 248)
      - * "Vice President Al Gore Visits TRW: Los Angeles Television Coverage," TRW Media Center, 22 Jun 1993 (Box 249)
      - "Air Force Base Closure," Alan Schwartz, Good Day L.A., KTTV, 15 Jul (Box 249)
      - "Anti-NAFTA Rally," 18 Aug (Box 249)
      - * "No on NAFTA, San Pedro rally," 18 Aug (Box 249)
      - "Visit to Northrop's F-18 Assembly Line," Northrop Aircraft Division, 30 Aug (Box 249)
      - * "Budget House Vote," Inside Politics with Eric Altsheel, 9 Sep (Box 249)
      - "Town Hall Meeting," 18 Sep (Box 249)
      - "Visit to Northrop F-18 Assembly Line," 12 Oct (Box 249)
      - "Gore/Perot," 9 Nov (Box 249)
      - * Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 3 Dec (Box 249)
      - * Interview regarding the resignation of Les Aspen [sic], CNN and Company; and C-SPAN hearing, 20 Dec (Box 249)
    - 1994
      - "Women in the Military," The World Today, CNN, 7 Jan 1994 (Box 250)
      - "Congresswoman Jane Harman's Visit to FMS Corporation," 20 Jan (Box 250)
      - "Harman Health Care Roundtable," 15 Feb (Box 250)
      - Land Conservancy award ceremony, 6 Apr (Box 250)
      - "F/A-18 Supplier Conference - Jane Harman," Northrop Aircraft Division, 20 Apr, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 250)
      - "Issues and Opinions: Gun Control," Town Hall Forum with Congresswoman Jane Harman, Paragon Cable, 6 May (Box 250)
      - "Health Care Roundtable," 19 May (Box 250)
      - "Brooks/Florence LWV Debate," May (Box 250)
      - * "Keynote Address: Jane Harmon [sic]," Law Enforcement for the 21st Century Conference, 20-22 Jun (Box 250)
      - "Congressional Visit: C-17 Program," McDonnell Douglas Teleproductions, Long Beach, CA, 8 Jul (Box 250)
      - "Jane Harman for Congress," Doak, Shrum, Harris, Carrier and Devine, 13 Oct, [reel-to-reel tape, see Box 247] (Box 250)
      - * "Harman: Border; Daily," Doak, Shrum, Harris, Carrier, and Devine, 1 Nov (Box 250)
      - CBS This Morning, 17 Nov 1994 (Box 251)
    - 1995
      - "Salute to Congress Dinner," 25 Jan (Box 251)
      - Rancho Palos Verdes city council meeting with Susan Brooks addressing spending issues put forward by Harman, Jan (Box 251)
      - "Defense Bills," CNN, 13 Feb, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 251)
      - "Jane Harman," 13 Feb [Betamax] (Box 251)
      - "Rep. Harman and TRP," House discussion of HR 889, 17 Feb (Box 251)
      - "Life and Times," 17 Mar (Box 251)
      - Week in Review, 17 Mar (Box 251)
      - Good Day LA, 7 Apr (Box 251)
      - * "Direct Access: Congresswoman Jane Harman," 19 Apr (Box 251)
      - Speech for District Art Competition, 22 May (Box 251)
      - * "The U.S. Congress and You: Representative Jane Harman," sponsored by Northrop Corporation, Andrew E. Manatos, Committee for Citizens Awareness, 22 Jun 1995, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 252)
      - "Week in Rock, Surfrider Pkg.," 23 Jun (Box 252)
      - "South Bay Report: Jane Harman," 11 Aug (Box 252)
      - "Raytheon Presents, Newsweek National Security Forum, Are We Ready for the New World Order?," 18 Sep (Box 252)
      - * Week in Review, 27 Oct (Box 252)
      - Week in Review with Bill Rosendahl, 3 Nov (Box 252)
      - "1995 Oversight Committee Hearings Regarding Jane Harman's 1992 Election" (Box 252)
    - 1996
      - "Strict New Flight Patterns Imposed at LAX," KNBC News, KCOP News, 13 Feb (Box 252)
      - "The Jane Harman Harbor Budget Roundtable," 15 Feb (Box 252)
      - "One on One with Congresswoman Jane Harman," 15 Feb (Box 252)
      - "Growing Dangers," 21 Feb; "LA's Filthy Secret," 3 May (Box 252)
      - "36th Congressional District," Bill Rosendahl interview of Republican congressional candidates, 7 Mar 1996 (Box 253)
      - "Adding Value for Our Customers: TRW Senior Management Briefing," TRW Media Center, Mar, [associated written material, see also Box 239] (Box 253)
      - "Law Enforcement Technology Conference: Lecture, Day 3," 11 Apr (Box 253)
      - * "Roundtable," Cox Communications, Inc., 23 May (Box 253)
      - "Paragon Cable Community Focus Interview," 24 Jun (Box 253)
      - * "An Interview with Jane Harman," Paragon Cable Community FOC, Jun (Box 253)
      - * "Crime Roundtable," The Aerospace Corporation, 3 Jul (Box 253)